const questions = [
    {
        question:"Which amongst the following is the largest mammal?",
        ans:"WHALE",
        level:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which animal exclusively eat only eucalyptus leaves and nothing else",
        ans:"KOALA",
        level:1
    },
    {
        question:"The animal having longest life span?",
        ans:"TORTOISE",
        level:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which is the largest living bird on Earth?",
        ans:"OSTRICH",
        level:1
    },
    {
        question:"What was the name of the first cloned sheep?",
        ans:"DOLLY",
        level:2
    },
    {
        question:"Pashmina shawl is made from the hair of?",
        ans:"GOAT",
        level:2
    },
    {
        question:"In which of the following animals is respiration done by skin?",
        ans:"DOLPHIN",
        level:2
    },
    {
        question:"Which animal do not make any sound?",
        ans:"GIRAFFE",
        level:2
    },
    {
        question:"Name the only animal that dislikes white colour?",
        ans:"TIGER",
        level:3
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following has the largest eyes of all land mammals?",
        ans:"HORSE",
        level:3
    },
    {
        question:"What is a rhinos horn made of ?",
        ans:"KERATIN",
        level:3
    },
    {
        question:"In which of the following animals is respiration done by skin?",
        ans:"FROG",
        level:3
    },
]

export default questions;